<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Campus View</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_building">BuildingActivity</string>
    <string-array name="buildings">
        <item>"Theater and Dance Building:This building houses the Department of Theater and Dance which fosters a vibrant and stimulating environment that encourages creative self-expression and critical thinking.  Undergraduate programs include intensive, conservatory-style training for actors and dancers, as well as general degrees with a focus on Dance, Design, Directing, Playwriting, Theater and Community and Theater and Performance Studies.  The department's nationally recognized and highly ranked graduate program offers a diverse array of interdisciplinary approaches to performance research within a global orientation.  The department provides a lively forum for faculty to integrate teaching and research, at the cutting edge of their areas of expertise."</item>
        <item>"Student Resource Building:Home of the Office of Student Life (OSL), Campus Learning Assistance Services (CLAS), and many more resources for students. OSL is the home of registered campus organizations, including fraternities and sororities, and student leadership development programs. CLAS is an academic support system that spans across humanities, social sciences, and STEM majors. CLAS offers classes and drop-in hours for additional help in a variety of classes. The Student Resource Building (SRB) is also home to Campus Advocacy Resources and Education (CARE), Disabled Students Program (DSP), Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), Resource Center for Sexual and Gender Diversity (RCSGD), Women, Gender and Sexual Equity (WGSE) and many more departments."</item>
        <item>"Events Center Thunderdome:The UCSB Events Center, aka the Thunderdome, is a multipurpose facility that strives to provide a clean, safe, well equipped venue where students, staff, faculty and community members can enjoy participating in athletic, academic, recreational or special events. This is where you could watch a basketball game or even a concert. Some of the acts played in the Thunderdome include YG, Snoop Dogg, Tchami, and Young the Giant."</item>
        <item>"Humanities and Social Sciences Building:HSSB is home to the Department of History, Classics, Religious Studies, and East Asian Language and Cultural Studies. All professors under any of these departments will have their offices in this building as well. The bottom floor also has several rooms for sections and lectures."</item>
        <item>"Arts Building:Housed in the Art Building, the Department of Art offers a dynamic, challenging, and open learning environment emphasizing interdisciplinary research and artistic production. At UCSB, emerging artists develop the means to express themselves and the critical thinking essential to their future roles within society. The Department of Art’s interdisciplinary curriculum structure is supplemented by close association with the Media Arts and Technology Graduate Program, the College of Creative Studies, and the Interdisciplinary Humanities Center. Within this building is also the Glassbox Gallery which showcases new and original work or various students each week."</item>
        <item>"Art, Design and Architecture Museum:The Art, Design and Architecture (AD&amp;A) Museum at the University of California, Santa Barbara provides intimate access to art. Through rotating installations of its permanent collections along with special exhibitions and programs, the ADandA Museum is both a teaching museum, committed to the development of critical thinking and visual literacy in support of the University’s goals of education, research, and service, and a resource for the wider Santa Barbara community. Towards the end of the year the ADandA Museum also exhibits students’ original art."</item>
        <item>"UCSB Bookstore:The top floor of the bookstore has various school supplies as well as some UCSB/Gaucho gear. The bottom floor has textbooks, lab notebooks, lab gear, and anything else required by professors for classes."</item>
        <item>"University Center:The University Center (or UCen) is the Student Union at UCSB offering a variety of products and services to students, faculty, staff, alumni and campus visitors. The UCen also provides jobs for approximately 500 students giving them learning experience outside of the classroom.  We strive to contribute to the intellectual, cultural, social and recreational life of the campus. The Ucen holds the UCSB Bookstore, SBprinter, the Hub, and Corwin Pavilion. SBprinter is great for any paid printing, though there are free places to print around up to 200 sheets per quarter. The Hub is a great venue for affordable concerts. Corwin Pavilion is one of the places that houses UCSB’s quarterly career fairs."</item>
        <item>"Storke Tower:Every UC campus has a bell tower and Storke Tower is UCSB’s. This tower houses a 61-bell carillon and every week a musician will play it as a free public concert. At 190 feet, Storke is the tallest structure in Southern Santa Barbara County. At the base (Storke Plaza), there is KCSB, UCSB’s student run radio show (tune in at 91.1 FM) and Daily Nexus, the official newsletter of UCSB."</item>
        <item>"Campbell Hall:Campbell Hall serves as a venue for Arts and Lectures films, performances, and guest speakers. This frequently-used facility is the largest auditorium on campus with 860 seats. Although Campbell Hall is often used as a classroom for large introductory courses, lower division classes at UCSB average 52 students while upper division classes average 36 students. Cheadle Hall houses the Office of Admissions and the academic advising office for the College of Letters and Science (LandS) where students are assisted in deciding on a major and scheduling their courses. LandS enrolls approximately 2,000 graduate students and 17,000 undergraduates in 72 majors and 41 minors. The Undergraduate Research and Creative Activities unit in LandS provides resources for students in all colleges to pursue independent research under the guidance of faculty mentors."</item>
        <item>"Ellison Hall:Ellison Hall is home to the Geography Department and is named after William Henry Ellison, Professor of History, Emeritus, and Doctor of Laws, 1878–1965. Dr. Ellison pioneered history instruction at Santa Barbara State College in 1924 and advocated the transfer of the institution from a state college to a University of California campus. That transfer occurred in 1944 when The Santa Barbara College of the University of California was established; at that time, Ellison was named chairman of the Department of Social Sciences, a position which he held until 1946. He became Professor Emeritus in 1948."</item>
        <item>"Phelps Hall:Phelps Hall was formerly the home to the Geography Department (now in Ellison) and now holds free printing labs and rooms for sections. Phelps Hall is named after Clarence L. Phelps (1881–1964), one of the first chancellors of what was to become UCSB. In 1918, he became president of Santa Barbara State Normal School of Manual Arts and Home Economics and in 1944 was appointed the first provost when the campus (then known as Santa Barbara State College) became a part of the University system, retiring from that position 1946."</item>
        <item>"Physical Science Building North:Physical Science Building North has numerous rooms for various lab classes. This building stands in front of a large green lawn known as the Chem Lawn or Engineering Lawn, as it is also in front of the Chemistry and Engineering buildings. Here you can usually find some dogs playing fetch or students relaxing in the sun."</item>
        <item>"Buchanan Hall:Buchanan Hall serves as a lecture hall for a wide variety of classes. Personally, I have had everything from Greek Literature to Introduction to Circuit Analysis in this building. Also in this hall is a little store, called the Buchanan Store, where students can purchase snacks, coffee, scantrons, and more."</item>
        <item>"Department of Chemistry and Biochemistry:The department offers the BA in chemistry, a BS in chemistry or biochemistry, and the MA, MS, and PhD degrees in chemistry. The department offers diverse experiences for students at all levels. From undergraduate courses where students build their own NMR instruments to graduate programs that offer research visits to China; the department excels at novel educational opportunities. Research faculty investigate many fascinating aspects of modern chemistry including research in solar energy conversion using plastics and applications of nanoscience to catalysis."</item>
        <item>"Carrillo Dining Commons:One of UCSB’s four dining commons. Right next to Manzanita Village and San Rafael which are common residence halls for second years. Students are required to have a meal plan if they live in one of the residence halls and have options of 10, 14, 17, or unlimited meals per week. All dining commons are served buffet style and the menus (which dietary restrictions) are online."</item>
        <item>"Ortega Dining Commons:One of UCSB’s four dining commons. Right next to the UCen and San Miguel residence hall. Students are required to have a meal plan if they live in one of the residence halls and have options of 10, 14, 17, or unlimited meals per week. All dining commons are served buffet style and the menus (which dietary restrictions) are online. Ortega is also where Jack Johnson, a UCSB alum, met his wife."</item>
        <item>"De La Guerra Dining Commons:One of UCSB’s four dining commons. Right next to the Chi-5 or Channel Island 5 (since the five residence halls are named after the Channel Islands) residence halls which are common amongst first years. Students are required to have a meal plan if they live in one of the residence halls and have options of 10, 14, 17, or unlimited meals per week. All dining commons are served buffet style and the menus (which dietary restrictions) are online. De La Guerra or DLG is known for late night which is a meal time that opens after dinner."</item>
        <item>"Manzanita Village Residence Hall:One of the popular residence options for second year students. This is more similar to apartments than typical dormitories. Features three and four story residential buildings with approximately 50 to 60 students each in single, double, small double, and triple occupancy rooms. Provides residence hall accommodations to more than 900 students, including 150 to 250 freshman students."</item>
        <item>"San Rafael Residence Hall:One of the popular residence options for second year students. This is more similar to apartments than typical dormitories. Home to 600 undergraduate students and conveniently close to Carrillo dining commons. Comprised of a 7-story tower and two 3-story buildings. There are 36 4-person suites, 12 6-person suites, 24 8-person suites, 36 doubles, and 114 singles."</item>
        <item>"San Miguel Residence Hall:One of the Chi-5, or Channel Island 5, residence halls located on main campus. Possibility of having an ocean view! It is eight-stories with each floor comprised of 24 to 25 students, where men and women are housed on alternating floors."</item>
        <item>"San Nicolas Residence Hall:One of the Chi-5, or Channel Island 5, residence halls located on main campus. Possibility of having an ocean view! Co-ed floors with men and women housed on separate wings. Mixture of double- and triple-occupancy rooms with limited single rooms available."</item>
        <item>"Santa Cruz Residence Hall:One of the Chi-5, or Channel Island 5, residence halls located on main campus. Possibility of having an ocean view! Similar to Anacapa and Santa Rosa in construction and location, known as a shortie. Two-story building connected by stairs. All rooms are triple occupancy, where men and women reside in adjacent wings on each floor."</item>
        <item>"Anacapa Residence Hall:One of the Chi-5, or Channel Island 5, residence halls located on main campus. Possibility of having an ocean view! Similar to Santa Cruz and Santa Rosa in construction and location, known as a shortie. Two-story building connected by stairs. All rooms are triple occupancy, where men and women reside in adjacent wings on each floor."</item>
        <item>"Santa Rosa Residence Hall:One of the Chi-5, or Channel Island 5, residence halls located on main campus. Similar to Anacapa and Santa Cruz in construction and location, known as a shortie. Two-story building connected by stairs. All rooms are triple occupancy, where men and women reside in adjacent wings on each floor."</item>
        <item>"South Hall:A six floor building that houses several departments including Math, English, and Chicano/Chicana Studies. On the second floor there is the EAP or Education Abroad Program. One in five students student abroad during their time at UCSB to one of our 300 plus programs offered on every continent but Antartica. "</item>
        <item>"Girvetz Hall:Girvetz Hall is home to several rooms that hold sections and lectures for various subjects. A cappella groups, such as Intervals and Naked Voices, also practice and preform in the larger lecture halls within Girvetz."</item>
        <item>"UCSB Library:This is our campus library, formerly known as the Davidson Library. The newer addition has 3 floors, where the bottom two offer a variety of study spaces and plenty of outlets. The original library is 8 floors and the top floor are quiet floors. Our library is just one of the many places to study on campus. We also have spaces in the UCen, Student Resource Building, and the residence halls."</item>
        <item>"College of Creative Studies:One of the three colleges, the other two being the College of Letters and Sciences (housed in Cheadle Hall) and College of Engineering (housed in Harold Frank Hall). This college offers more opportunities for research while allowing students in these programs more flexibility. This tiny building is fitting for this tiny college that only has 300 to 400 students total."</item>
        <item>"Harold Frank Hall:Home to the College of Engineering academic advisors. Has several rooms for labs including CSIL, Computer Science Instructional Lab, Also, were you can find the staff and faculty for Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, and Computer Science."</item>
        <item>"Broida Hall:Department of Physics as well as lecture halls and labs for physics classes. There are multiple physics series for physics majors, engineers, and other STEM majors so it is likely you will have a class here."</item>
        <item>"Engineering II:Home to the other engineering majors faculty and staff (Chemical Engineering and Mechanical Engineering). This is where those two majors will likely meet with professors and have various labs. There is also the Courtyard Cafe in the far corner of the building which is great for a quick meal or snack."</item>
        <item>"Mosher Alumni House:Holds several various events, usually for alumni. During finals week, it is another good, quiet place to study that has snacks!"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_routes">RoutesActivity</string>
</resources>
